# TOLULOPE FLOSBACH

# FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER



+2348080136863



tolulopeflosbach@gmail.com



12 Gerrard Road, Ikoyi, Lagos, Nigeria

I am a qualified and professional web developer with a strong background in web and mobile app development and design. I have experience in programming and debugging and can offer marketing experience in addition to upgraded web development skills.

#### EXPERIENCE

# WEB DESIGNER/WEB DEVELOPER 2016 - 2021 | Eman Zazar Limited

- Built, designed and maintained company's main webpage, 2 online stores and 1 company blog.
- · Carried out debugging exercises on all company sites to better user experience which in turn drove sales conversion rate up by 46%.
- Built and designed the web store Falke Nigeria, a subsidiary of German clothing brand, Falke.
- Purchased and managed the Domain names, Name servers and zones for all company web pages.
- Mapped all domain names to the web hosting server.
- Incorporated personalised company emails for the staff.
- Created graphics design to improve the look and feel of the company web pages

#### **HEAD OF EXTERNAL CONTENT**

### 2015 - 2016 | Pulse Nigeria (Ringier Group, Switzerland)

- Sourced, edited and managed external content for one of Africa's largest online news paper.
- Developed creative content alongside other content creators to drive external content traffic metrics up by 80% within 6 months.

# ADVERTISING AND BRAND MANAGER 2012 - 2015 | DDB Worldwide

- Worked with world renowned advertising agency to create campaigns for big telecommunication brands.
- · Developed marketing campaigns across different media channels such as Television commercials, billboard advertising, print media and social media marketing.
- Conceptualised strategies for new businesses and participated in advertising pitches.

## PROJECTS & PORTFOLIO

**GITHUB** 

• https://github.com/Cocoflosbach

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/tolulope-coco-flosbach/

# EDUCATION

2021 - 2022

**CAREER FOUNDRY** 

Fullstack web development

2020-2020

HAVARD BUSINESS SCHOOL **CORe (Credential of readiness)** 

2018 - 2012

**COVENANT UNIVERSITY** Bachelor of Sciences, Mass Communication

Second class honours (upper division)

#### SKILLS

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Javascript
- Node.js
- React.js/ React Native
- SQL/PostgreSQL
- NoSQL/MongoDB, Firestore
- **Problem-Solving**
- Adaptability

# OTHER CERTIFICATIONS

• Diploma in graphics design, New Horizons (2017)

## LANGUAGES

#### **FNGLISH**

Native speaker

#### **GERMAN**

Proficient